
RELAPSE is a 100% handmade and FREE font both for personal and commercial use, even the tool it's made with is D.I.Y. which is a folded pen made out of soda can. 

This font is ALL uppercase characters but the glyphs in place of the lowercase set you find a different version of each letter so you can play around and combine upper and lowercase in order to get the best and more natural result. The character set covers all Western and Eastern European accents and special characters.

There are some ligatures for :
TT FA IJ ST TH TO
and
a stylistic alternate for letter "O" (underlined "O")

For downloading the FREE commercial license please visit :

https://rolandhuse.com

Again, the font is entirely free to use for all kinds of projects from personal to packaging and branding etc. However, crediting or donations are always much appreciated. 

Follow and see more of my work (or for eventual updates in the future on this font) on

instagram.com/rolandhusedesign

Have a Great Day and good luck with your creative work!

Roland

* * *

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.

You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.

You MAY NOT redistribute this font.



